Mitch Bilensky

General tech enthusiast with an interest in cloud development and architecture, DevOps, and home automation. Has been working as a full stack developer for the past 6 years mostly within Java (Spring) and JS (React and Angular), with a recent focus on the cloud

Woodmount Dr Fredericton, NB E3A 2M4 (506) 461-0630 mitch.bilensky@gmail.com mitch.bilensky.ca

EXPERIENCE

Accreon, Fredericton — Team Lead

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

Lead a scrum team of developers contracted for planning, building, deploying, and maintaining a series of cloud services used by a leading electronic health record platform.

Built, maintained, deployed a series of Java/React services hosted in Azure AKS and deployed using Jenkins, Helm and ArgoCD, integrated with an EHR system.

Accreon, Fredericton—Full Stack Developer

APRIL 2015 - APRIL 2021

Worked within a team of developers consulting for a large electronic health record system and built various solutions within their monolith style app including:

- A document management system used to populate template files with user data, and integrating with an eSignature vendor used to digitally sign the generated documents.
- A CRM-style solution for managing new users and tracking their onboarding progress.
- A set of APIs for supporting the mobile version of the CRM solution.

Built and maintained a series of Java services within a large-scale EHR system and integrated with other 3rd party eSignature vendors

EDUCATION

New Brunswick Community College, Fredericton — *IT: Programmer Analyst*

SEPT 2013 - JUNE 2015

Graduated from New Brunswick's community college program with honours including a co-op program

SKILLS

Java -- Spring (MVC, Boot, Data, etc.), JPA, Flowable, JUnit,

JavaScript -- React, Redux, TypeScript, Angular, Cypress, Jest

AWS -- CloudFormation, S3, CloudFront, DynamoDB, Cognito, IAM

DevOps -- Jenkins, Helm, ArgoCD, GitLab CI, Github Actions

Infrastructure as Code --AWS CloudFormation/SAM, Terraform

Tools -- Git, Docker, Maven, NPM